Robert was on board, so later that week
I hired a professional tailor to help
design the chili suit based on a
detailed sketch I had drawn.
The easiest way is probably to put the
chili in.
I guess from the neck part, right?
Sure. Our plan was to have the chili
reservoirs mimic the distribution of fat
on a larger man's body, so it wouldn't
look suspicious under clothing. And with
the help of a guy from Craigslist, our
tailor was able to take all the
measurements he needed.
The chili is going to go here.
Mhm.
Then we're going to get it more in here,
too.
Mhm. You could probably do like a cup
there, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Cup or so?
a cup, yeah.
Yeah, okay. All right, so we'll see you
around, then. Yeah, thank you so much.
And a few days later, we received a
completed prototype of the
heat-resistant polyvinyl chloride suit
designed to hold over 100 servings of
fresh chili.
The individual reservoirs would be
linked by a network of tubes that would
all lead to a battery-powered
peristaltic pump for dispensing the
chili.
Using our intake funnel, we loaded in
over 30 lb of Robert's product that had
been blended into a thin paste to ensure
an even flow without compromising the
flavor.
So with that, I activated the pump, and
it was time to see if this could work.
As I had hoped, the pump dispensed the
chili at a steady pace, which was good.
But I realized we had overlooked a
crucial detail. The chili suit prevented
bathroom access, and because of its
weight, removing it during a game would
not be an option.
So I experimented with a design that
would allow me to deposit my excretions
directly into custom rubber underwear
connected to a secondary pumping system,
so I could eject it into a toilet via a
second tube down my right arm.
But once I had some clothing on, I
realized the potential for a costly
mix-up was too great. So I had the
bottom part of the suit redesigned with
strategic holes in the groin and
buttocks region that would allow the
wearer to relieve him or herself without
taking off the suit.
But, there was still the issue of the
temperature. To meet health department
standards, Robert said the chili would
have to remain above 135°
F
at all times. But, when I put it on, the
heat was so intense that I could barely
have it against my skin for more than a
few seconds. So, I tracked down some
heat-resistant polymer gel that could
insulate the body against the most
extreme temperatures.
Feel anything?
No.
Good.
I did a preliminary test with a
blowtorch on various parts of my body to
ensure the gel would protect even my
most sensitive regions.
Oh.
And after gelled up from head to toe,
the burning sensation had completely
vanished.
Yeah.
It seemed like we had solved every
problem. But, there was still one final
thing I had to take care of.
The pump on my chest that made the chili
suit function was made out of metal. And
to get into Rabobank Arena, every ticket
holder has to pass through a metal
detector. So, I figured if I could
convince security that I had a medically
necessary pacemaker, they wouldn't be
suspicious when the alarm went off. So,
I taped a real pacemaker to my chest and
then headed to a walk-in clinic to
request an x-ray that would hopefully
trick the physician into writing me a
doctor's note.
Oh, I would need to actually examine you
and see
why is it that you need the x-ray. I
have to have a reason why.
Well, I'm paying you for it, so what do
you care?
I'm actually
legally it's it's being
um
monitored to see why we're ordering an
x-ray.
Oh.
Well, what's the minimum I need to say
to get
Um either some area hurts of your of
your chest or you're having a cough.
Okay.
Yeah.
Are you What are you experiencing?
Yeah, both those. Yeah.
Okay.
Do something as close as you can and
you're going to take the shirt off,
okay?
Okay. Um
I'm a little self-conscious about my
body. Would it be okay if I left at
least my undershirt on?
Your undershirt will be fine, but I got
to get rid of the buttons, okay?
Okay. Okay, sure.
Okay, buddy, take a big breath.
Hold it.
And once the doctor saw the pacemaker on
my X-ray,
It looks like it's in well position and
and uh
no abnormalities.
She wrote me a doctor's note that would
hopefully get me through security.
Thank you so much, doctor.
And that meant it was finally time to
buy a ticket for the next Bakersfield
Condors home game.